[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Creative thinking is the ability to generate __________ ideas.",
    "options": [
      "innovative",
      "unconventional",
      "useful",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "__________ are representative items within each concept.",
    "options": [
      "Constructs",
      "Symbols",
      "Prototypes",
      "Categories"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "A mental representation can take the form of a",
    "options": [
      "word",
      "image",
      "sound",
      "all of the given"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following is true?",
    "options": [
      "Thinking is a lower mental process",
      "Thinking is a sub-vocal talking",
      "Thinking is unrelated to problem solving",
      "We can only think in numbers or words"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Cognitive architecture is a theory about the __________ structures that create a mind in natural or artificial systems.",
    "options": [
      "structures",
      "facts",
      "images",
      "sounds"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Bloom's Taxonomy is a system of hierarchical models (arranged in a hierarchical rank,) used to categorize __________ into varying levels of complexity.",
    "options": [
      "learning objectives",
      "attention goals",
      "prototypes",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "__________ knowledge refers to knowledge of terminology and specific details.",
    "options": [
      "Metacognitive",
      "Conceptual",
      "Kinesthetic",
      "Factual"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Choosing to skim subheadings of unimportant information to get to the information we need as a metacognitive skill is called",
    "options": [
      "Skimming",
      "Rehearsing",
      "Self-monitoring",
      "Modifying"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "__________ refers to the ability to regulate your thoughts and set aside any personal biases to come to the best conclusion.",
    "options": [
      "Self-regulation",
      "Openmindedness",
      "Observation",
      "Interpretation",
      "elaboration"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "__________ method of solving problems refers to a rule that guarantees the solution to a problem",
    "options": [
      "imagination.",
      "trial and error",
      "analogy",
      "algorithm"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  }
]